Guide to the Phi Beta Kappa, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1786-1951; Accession 1952-A-001
  - Election by class, 1962-1969 (Box 10, Folder 301)
  - Election lists by class: 1946, 1946M, 1948, 1950, 1951, 1954-1958, no date (Box 10, Folder 302)
  - Guide for selection of members, partial copy, undated (Box 10, Folder 303)
  - Hadley, James, Extracts from the diary of, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 304)
  - Lists by class, 1916-1926 (Box 10, Folder 305)
  - Lists of Honorary members, 1767-1924 (Box 10, Folder 306)
  - Minutes of meetings, 1826 September 12-1940 February 27 (Box 10, Folder 307)
  - ØBK certificate of Ray Forbes Jordon ANS Hollon A. Farr, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 308)
  - Photograph S. Bayne Jones, BA 1910, and C.B. Warren PhB 1896 (Box 10, Folder 309)
  - Scrapbooks, 1896-1911 (Box 10, Folder 310 - 311)
  - Students in ØBK, 1938-1944 (Box 10, Folder 312)
  - Yale Daily News, 1940 February 27 (Box 10, Folder 313)
  - Unmounted clippings from the Yale Daily News, 1910-1931 (Box 11, Folder 314)
  - ØBK Orations, 1797-1887 (Box 11, Folder 315 - 317)
  - Orations and poems, 1822-1868 (Box 12, Folder 318)
  - Minutes of meetings, 1895-[1904] (Box 12, Folder 319)
  - Register Book, [1787-1858] (Box 12, Folder 320)
  - Catalogue of contents in trunk, 1772-1898 (Box 13, Folder 321)
  - Catalogue of members, annotated, bound copy of printer's proof, 1905 (Box 13, Folder 322)
- Records, 1961-1979; Accession 1981-A-051
  Restricted until January 1, 2054
  - Correspondence and lists, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arrears, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Elections, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Election, 1970 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Election, 1970 November (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Election, 1971 June (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Election, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Election: original list, 1971 October (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Current bills, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Election, 1972 June (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Election, 1978 June (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Election, 1973 October (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Election, 1974 May (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Election, 1974 October (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Election master sheets, 1974 October (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Election, 1975 October (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Election, 1975 May (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Election master sheets, 1972 October (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Election master sheets, 1976 October (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Election, 1976 May (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Election, 1976 October (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Election, 1976 October (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Election, 1976 November (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Triennial, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Election, 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Election, 1977 November (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Fall Election master letters, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Fall Election, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Election, 1978 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Fourth Election, 1978 October 24 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Election master sheets, 1978 September 19 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Election, 1978 September 19 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Election master sheets, 1979 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Election, 1979 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Election, 1979 September 19 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Election master sheets, 1979 September 19 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Records, 1969-1984; Accession 1988-A-064
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2020
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Elections, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Commencement Election, Master Sheets, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Commencement Election, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Election Master Sheets, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Elections, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Elections, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Commencement Election, Master Sheets, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Commencement Election, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Election Master Sheets, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Election Correspondence, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Commencement Election, Master Sheets, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Commencement Election, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Commencement Election, Master Copy, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Commencement Election, Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Election, Master Copies, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Election, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Membership
    - Faculty Member List, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - United Chapters, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Officers, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Members: Survey, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Nominations Committee, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - PBK Keys of William and Mabel Devane: have been transferred to the objects collection, YRG 45-D, 3 (Box 1)
  - Speeches and Addresses
    - Paul Horgan, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Donald Kagan, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Martin J. Klein, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - E.S. Morgan, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - G.W. Pierson, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Maxine Singer, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - H.D. Taft, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - C. Vann Woodward, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Financial Material
    - Finances, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Phi Beta Kappa records, 1966-1973; Accession 2000-A-002
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet Follow-up, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Speaker, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Medalists, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cobb and Solomon on Phi Beta Kappa (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Graduate members (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Speaker, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Medalists, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Faculty Members (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Initiation, 1971, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Medalists, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Speaker, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Honorary Members (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Griffin (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - G.W. Pierson Phi Beta Kappa Dodo, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Medalists, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa May, 1970 May (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Initiation, 1967, 1968, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Members (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Speaker, 1969, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Writer, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Current, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Election Standards (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Associates -- Seward (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Constitution etc. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Documents (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet and follow up, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Silk (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet Documents, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Medalists, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Catiloryn (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet and follow up, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet Speaker, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Medalists, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet Follow up, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Dope on Medalists and Speakers, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet, 1967 April (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Plans for 1967 Banquet (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Initiation, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Banquet Speeches, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Follow up, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - A.B. Crawford and Phi Beta Kappa History (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - De Vane Medals (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Crawford Phi Beta Kappa (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Phi Beta Kappa G.W. Pierson #235 Council, 1970 September (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Glass Report (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - United Chapters of Phi Beta Kappa (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - G.W. Pierson Unfiled Materials (Box 2)
- Phi Beta Kappa cryptogram, undated; Accession 2009-A-174
  - Phi Beta Kappa cryptogram, undated (Box 1)
- Yale chapter charter, 1789; Accession 2015-A-037
  - Yale chapter charter, 1789 (Box 1, Folder 1)